[
  {
    "phrases": [
      {
        "question": "Alex!",
        "reply": "What? We ____ be at home in five hours.",
        "answers": [
          "are",
          "won't",
          "will"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "But our airplane pilot was killed two hours ago.",
        "reply": "____ we be at home?",
        "answers": [
          "Will",
          "Won’t",
          "Don't"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Yes, but I have tickets to Moscow.",
        "reply": "____ we be in Moscow in five hours?",
        "answers": [
          "Do",
          "Will",
          "Don't"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Yes, but there are bears in Russia.",
        "reply": "...We ____ be in Moscow.",
        "answers": [
          "won't",
          "will",
          "are"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "phrases": [
      {
        "question": "Alex!",
        "reply": "What? We ____ be at home in five hours.",
        "answers": [
          "are",
          "won't",
          "will"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "But our airplane pilot was killed two hours ago.",
        "reply": "____ we be at home?",
        "answers": [
          "Will",
          "Won’t",
          "Don't"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Yes, but I have tickets to Moscow.",
        "reply": "____ we be in Moscow in five hours?",
        "answers": [
          "Do",
          "Will",
          "Don't"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Yes, but there are bears in Russia.",
        "reply": "...We ____ be in Moscow.",
        "answers": [
          "won't",
          "will",
          "are"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "phrases": [
      {
        "question": "Alex!",
        "reply": "What? We ____ be at home in five hours.",
        "answers": [
          "are",
          "won't",
          "will"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "But our airplane pilot was killed two hours ago.",
        "reply": "____ we be at home?",
        "answers": [
          "Will",
          "Won’t",
          "Don't"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Yes, but I have tickets to Moscow.",
        "reply": "____ we be in Moscow in five hours?",
        "answers": [
          "Do",
          "Will",
          "Don't"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Yes, but there are bears in Russia.",
        "reply": "...We ____ be in Moscow.",
        "answers": [
          "won't",
          "will",
          "are"
        ],
        "answerIndex": 0
      }
    ]
  }
]